<QUOTES>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Napoleon Hill</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Napoleon_Hill_headshot.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Oliver Napoleon Hill (born October 26, 1883 - November 8, 1970) was an American self-help author. He is known best for his book Think and Grow Rich (1937) which is among the 10 best selling self-help books of all time.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Napoleon Hill</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Napoleon_Hill_headshot.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Oliver Napoleon Hill (born October 26, 1883 - November 8, 1970) was an American self-help author. He is known best for his book Think and Grow Rich (1937) which is among the 10 best selling self-help books of all time.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Albert Einstein</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/BoilingUnawareBedbug.gif
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Albert Einstein (14 March 1879 - 18 April 1955) was a German-born theoretical physicist who developed the theory of relativity, one of the two pillars of modern physics
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Robert Frost</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Two roads diverged in a wood, and I took the one less traveled by, And that has made all the difference.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Robert-Frost-9303322-1-402.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Robert Lee Frost (March 26, 1874 - January 29, 1963) was an American poet.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Florence Nightingale</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
I attribute my success to this: I never gave or took any excuse.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/article-2255095-00280EEF00000258-322_634x628.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Florence Nightingale (12 May 1820 - 13 August 1910) was an English social reformer and statistician, and the founder of modern nursing.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Wayne Gretzky</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>You miss 100% of the shots you don’t take.</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/wayne-gretzky.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Wayne Douglas Gretzky CC (born January 26, 1961) is a Canadian former professional ice hockey player and former head coach.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Michael Jordan</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
I've missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I've lost almost 300 games. 26 times I've been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I've failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/michael-jordan-2-paul-meijering.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Michael Jeffrey Jordan (born February 17, 1963), also known by his initials, MJ, is an American former professional basketball player.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Amelia Earhart</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
The most difficult thing is the decision to act, the rest is merely tenacity.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/AmeliaEarhart_PittGirl.jpg</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Amelia Mary Earhart (born July 24, 1897; disappeared July 2, 1937) was an American aviation pioneer and author. Earhart was the first female aviator to fly solo across the Atlantic Ocean.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Babe Ruth</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Every strike brings me closer to the next home run.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/babe-ruth.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
George Herman "Babe" Ruth Jr. (February 6, 1895 - August 16, 1948) was an American professional baseball player whose career in Major League Baseball (MLB) spanned 22 seasons, from 1914 through 1935.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>W. Clement Stone</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Definiteness of purpose is the starting point of all achieve
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/W-Clement-Stone.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
William Clement Stone (May 4, 1902 - September 3, 2002) was a businessman, philanthropist and New Thought self-help book author.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Kevin Kruse</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Life isn't about getting and having, it's about giving and being.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/kruse-k.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Kevin M. Kruse is a professor of history at Princeton University. He served as the David L. Rike University Preceptor of History from 2003 to 2006. His research interests include the political, social, and urban/suburban history of 20th-century America, with a particular focus on the making of modern conservatism.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>John Lennon</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Life is what happens to you while you’re busy making other plans.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/13858.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
John Winston Ono Lennon (9 October 1940 - 8 December 1980) was an English singer, songwriter, and peace activist who co-founded the Beatles
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Earl Nightingale</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>. We become what we think about.</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/earl.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Earl Nightingale (March 12, 1921 - March 25, 1989) was an American radio speaker and author, dealing mostly with the subjects of human character development, motivation, and meaningful existence.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Mark Twain</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn’t do than by the ones you did do, so throw off the bowlines, sail away from safe harbor, catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore, Dream, Discover.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/testemonials.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Samuel Langhorne Clemens (November 30, 1835 - April 21, 1910), better known by his pen name Mark Twain, was an American writer, humorist, entrepreneur, publisher, and lecturer.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Charles Swindoll</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/G1Gy0VCa_400x400.jpeg</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Charles Rozell "Chuck" Swindoll (born October 18, 1934) is an evangelical Christian pastor, author, educator, and radio preacher.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Alice Walker</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
The most common way people give up their power is by thinking they don’t have any.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/alice-walker.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Alice Walker (born February 9, 1944) is an American novelist, short story writer, poet, and activist. She wrote the novel The Color Purple.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Buddha</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>The mind is everything. What you think you become. </TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/bigstock-Statue-of-Buddha-67129324.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Gautama Buddha (c. 563/480  - c. 483/400 BCE), after the title of Buddha, was an ascetic and sage, on whose teachings Buddhism was founded. He is believed to have lived and taught mostly in the eastern part of ancient India sometime between the 6th and 4th centuries BCE.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Socrates</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>An unexamined life is not worth living.</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Socrates-800x800.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Socrates ( c. 470 - 399 BC) was a classical Greek (Athenian) philosopher credited as one of the founders of Western philosophy, and as being the first moral philosopher, of the Western ethical tradition of thought.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Woody Allen</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>Eighty percent of success is showing up.</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/545.jpg</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Heywood Allen (born Allan Stewart Konigsberg; December 1, 1935) is an American director, writer, actor, comedian, and musician whose career spans more than six decades.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Steve Jobs</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Your time is limited, so don’t waste it living someone else’s life.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Steve-Jobs-Justin-SullivanGetty-Images-The-Gentlemans-Journal-Square.jpg</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Steven Paul Jobs (February 24, 1955 - October 5, 2011) was an American entrepreneur and business magnate. He was the chairman, chief executive officer (CEO), and a co-founder of Apple Inc., chairman and majority shareholder of Pixar, a member of The Walt Disney Company's board of directors following its acquisition of Pixar, and the founder, chairman, and CEO of NeXT.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Vince Lombardi</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>Winning isn’t everything, but wanting to win is.</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Lombardi-Vince-2.jpg</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Vincent Thomas Lombardi (June 11, 1913 - September 3, 1970) was an American football player, coach, and executive in the National Football League (NFL).
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Stephen Covey</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/images.jpeg</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Stephen Richards Covey (October 24, 1932 - July 16, 2012) was an American educator, author, businessman, and keynote speaker. His most popular book is The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Pablo Picasso</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Every child is an artist. The problem is how to remain an artist once he grows up.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/ourartists-1.jpg</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Pablo Ruiz Picasso (25 October 1881 - 8 April 1973) was a Spanish painter, sculptor, printmaker, ceramicist, stage designer, poet and playwright who spent most of his adult life in France.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Christopher Columbus</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
You can never cross the ocean until you have the courage to lose sight of the shore.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Christopher_Columbus.0.0.PNG</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Christopher Columbus (before 31 October 1451 - 20 May 1506) was an Italian explorer, navigator, and colonizer. Born in the Republic of Genoa, Columbus, under the auspices of the Catholic Monarchs of Spain, completed four voyages across the Atlantic Ocean. Those voyages, and his efforts initiated the permanent European colonization of the New World.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Maya Angelou</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
I’ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/1373573331_Maya-Angelou-9185388-2-402.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Maya Angelou (born Marguerite Annie Johnson; April 4, 1928 - May 28, 2014) was an American poet, singer, memoirist, and civil rights activist.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Jim Rohn</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>Either you run the day, or the day runs you.</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/artworks-000102755618-vagzoy-t500x500.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Emanuel James "Jim" Rohn (September 17, 1930 - December 5, 2009) was an American entrepreneur, author and motivational speaker.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Henry Ford</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Whether you think you can or you think you can’t, you’re right.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/henry-ford-9298747-1-402.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Henry Ford (July 30, 1863 - April 7, 1947) was an American captain of industry and a business magnate, the founder of the Ford Motor Company, and the sponsor of the development of the assembly line technique of mass production.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Johann Wolfgang von Goethe</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Whatever you can do, or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/d150107a6b2b940be48a3a9642364042r.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Johann Wolfgang von Goethe (28 August 1749 - 22 March 1832) was a German writer and statesman.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Frank Sinatra</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>The best revenge is massive success.</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/frank-sinatra-9484810-3-402.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Francis Albert Sinatra (December 12, 1915 - May 14, 1998) was an American singer, actor, and producer who was one of the most popular and influential musical artists of the 20th century.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Zig Ziglar</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
People often say that motivation doesn’t last. Well, neither does bathing. That’s why we recommend it daily.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/Zig_photo.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Hilary Hinton "Zig" Ziglar (November 6, 1926 - November 28, 2012) was an American author, salesman, and motivational speaker.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
<QUOTE>
<AUTHOR>Anais Nin</AUTHOR>
<TEXT>
Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage.
</TEXT>
<IMAGE>
    http://web.sfc.keio.ac.jp/~t17600sy/FIT2/MiniProject/images/nin-anais-image.jpg
</IMAGE>
<INFO>
Angela Anais Juana Antolina Rosa Edelmira Nin y Culmell (February 21, 1903 - January 14, 1977), known professionally as Anais Nin, was a French-American diarist, essayist, novelist, and writer of short stories and erotica.
</INFO>
</QUOTE>
</QUOTES>
